{
    "category": "Category",
    "title": "Work Questions",
    "difficulty": "Difficulty",
    "difficultyOptions": {
        "easy": "Easy",
        "medium": "Medium",
        "hard": "Hard"
    },
    "questions": {
        "easy": [
            { "question": "What number of working hours do you prefer per day?", "answers": [ "8", "4", "16" ]},
            { "question": "Where do you prefer to work?", "answers": [ "Somewhere remote", "In office", "Among collegues" ]},
            { "question": "What does working place means to you?", "answers": [ "Second Life", "Chair", "Approriate conditions" ]},
            { "question": "Is the number of working hours related with the quality of work?", "answers": [ "No", "Depends", "Yes" ]}
        ],
        "medium": [
            { "question": "Is rest important?", "answers": [ "It is vital", "No", "Depends" ]},
            { "question": "Desire/will for work?", "answers": [ "Yes, it's important", "Discipline", "Motivation/Causality" ]},
            { "question": "Quality of work done?", "answers": [ "big quantity of practice", "Focusing", "Comunnication" ]},
            { "question": "What is the good working process (workflow)?", "answers": [ "Organizing/approaches", "Methodical", "Practice and experience" ]}
        ],
        "hard": [
            { "question": "Achieving high standard?", "answers": [ "Work with high quality", "Experience", "Discipline" ]},
            { "question": "Vacation?", "answers": [ "Yes, of course", "No, it is not possible", "There is no such thing" ]},
            { "question": "Order in working process (workflow)?", "answers": [ "Target, Practice, Results", "Target, Focusing, Results", "Target, Organizing, Results" ]},
            { "question": "Results from work?", "answers": [ "High, due to quality", "Positive, due to experience", "Something else ..." ]}
        ]
    }
}